

CONTACT

- +358 45 1306 412
- $oxedsymbol{^{\prime\prime}}$ jonasjulin1@hotmail.com
- Eestintaival 3A1, 02280 Espoo, Finland
- Linkedin:
 https://www.linkedin.com/in/jonasju
 lin1/
 Personal(WIP):

https://jonzsa92.github.io/paasivu.ht

EDUCATION

1998-2010

EUROPEAN SCHOOL OF LUXEMBURG, LUXEMBURG

2022-

HAAGA-HELIA UNIVERSITY OF APPLIED SCIENCES

BBA - IT

Data infrastructure & Cloud

Services

LANGUAGES

- Finnish (Native)
- Swedish (Native)
- English (Fluent C1)
- German (Intermediate)
- French (Poor)

SKILLS

- Teamwork
- Effective communication
- Time Management
- Attention to work-detail
- Good Customer Service skills

JONAS JULIN

CUSTOMER SERVICE SPECIALIST & STUDENT

PROFILE

I am working and studying simultaneously. My current position is a Customer Service Specialist in retail at Joblink Oy. I am studying a degree of Bachelor of Business Administration in the field of Informatics, with a specialization in Data Infrastructure and Cloud Services.

I am quick to learn and adopt new things. I am good at working in time-demanding tasks, and I always focus on the quality of my work. Thanks to my studies and my free time, I am skilled with computers and information technology.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Joblink Oy

2019 - PRESENT

Customer Service Specialist, Retail

• General customer service tasks in retail shops, such as refilling shelves, customer service, team-leading and overseeing departments.

Asianajotoimisto Lakiakatemia

Intern, Office Assistant

29/02/2016 - 14/03/2016 (104h)

- Office work, such as scheduling meetings, drafting legal documents and customer service.
- Internship was required for Law Studies at the time.

Stockmann

Intern, Customer Service

04/2012 - 06/2012

Customer service internship that was required for studies at the time.
 Included general customer service tasks as well as working the counter and cashier.

IT SKILLS

- Windows OS and its environment
- iOS (basics)
- Linux OS and its environment (Debian)
- Microsoft Office/365 programs
- Adobe Photoshop
- Adobe After Effects (basics)
- Java basics
- JavaScript basics
- Python basics

- Linux servers
- Windows servers (w/ Hyper-V)
- Microsoft Azure Basics
- AWS (basics)